"addon"
{
  "addon_game_name"                               "Petri Reborn" 
  "addon_game_description"                        "It is a big humor battle between stylish, trendy, youth KVN's and old, dull, soaked mothballs inhabitants of Crooked Mirror headed by Petrosyan."
  "how_to_play"                                   "How to play"
  "game_info_Petrosyan"                           "Petrosyan and his henchmans need to laugh to death all KVN's."
  "game_info_KVNs"                                "KVN's want to avoid humoristic casting into Crooked Mirror and to find an exit from film set."
  "game_info_tips_header"                         "Usefull tips:"
  
  "game_info_tip_petro01"                               "1. KVN's have three resource types: gold, lumber and food. Lumber can be gathered almost everywhere; gold generates by gold towers, will be good to build it in safe place; amount of food depends of tents count." 
  
  "game_info_tip_kvn01"                               "2. Petrosyan and his henchmans have access to shop with humorictic tools. There are some arena's nearby to raise his humoritic power. They works only at daytime. It's recommended to use it to get gold and expirience. Petrosyan's army must search and laugh KVN's at night."
  "game_info_tip_kvn02"                               "3. If where are a lot of players in KVN's team, it's desirable to spread bases to different places of the map to have more place and to make Petrosyan's life harder."

  "score_gold"                                    "Gold"
  "score_lumber"                                  "Lumber"
  "score_food"                                    "Food"

	"Unassigned"      								"Unassigned Team"
	"Spectator"       								"Spectator Team"
	"Neutrals"        								"Neutral Team"
	"NoTeam"          								"No Team"

	"DOTA_GoodGuys"   								"KVN"
	"DOTA_BadGuys"    								"PETROSES"

  "area_claimed"                                  "You have chosen your zone"
  "you_cant_build"                                "You can't build here"

  "petrosyan_is_killed" "PETROSYAN IS KILLED BY "
  "kvn_fan_is_dead" " IS LAUGHING"

  "exit_notification"  "KVN FANS CAN START TO BUILD EXIT"
  "exit_warning"  "YOU HAVE 4 MINUTES TO START EXIT CONSTRUCTION"

  "kvn_win"                                       "Exit built! Bye, Petrosyan!"
  "petrosyan_win"                                 "Petrosyan was laughed all....."
  "petrosyan_limit"  "CASTING IS OVER AND YOU DIDNT ESCAPE!!! AHAHAHAH"

  "gather_more_lumber"                            "Gather more lumber"
  "need_more_food"                                "Build or upgrade tents"

  "repair_target_is_full"                         "Target doesn't need repair"
  "repair_target_is_not_a_building"               "It's not a building"

  "start_game"                                    "CASTING TO CROOKED MIRROR HAS BEGAN SOON!!! RUN WHILE YOU CAN!!"
  "petrosyan_is_awake"                            "PETROSYAN WOKE UP!!! АHАHAHАHАHА"

  "no_farm_tonight"                               "NIGHT IS NOT A TIME FOR FARM!!! KILL KVN's!!"

  "petri_start"                                   "GOOD TIME FOR FARM. TAKE YOUR LAUGHING TOOLS AND WAIT FOR THE NIGHT TO KILL IMPUDENT KVN's"

  "you_cant_be_here"                              "YOU DON'T WANT TO GO THERE!"

  "exit_construction_is_started"                  "KVN's FAN STARTS TO BUILD EXIT!!!"

  "sputnik_launched" "You seeing a small point in the sky. ААаАаААаААаА IT'S PETROSYAN'S SATELLITE!!!!"

  "too_early_for_exit" "YOU CAN BUILD EXIT ONLY AFTER 20 MIN MARK"
}